Finding aid to the Classes of 2001-2006 records CA.MS.01029
Smith College Archives
Classes of 2001-2006 records
1997-2006
Smith College Archives
Smith College. Class of 2001.
CA.MS.01029
2.708 linear feet (8 containers)
College Archives has been collecting class material dating back to the Class of 1879. The Classes of 2001-2006 records consist of individual class notes, examinations, papers and class letters, correspondence, photographs, scrapbooks, songbooks as well as reunion materials of the same nature, all related to or dating from the time periods during which these classes were students at Smith College.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for use with following restrictions on access:
Box 2317.1 is restricted until 2052
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Whenever donation information for a particular set of material is known, it is included in the finding aid below. However, a majority of the material was not formally accessioned and its origins are not currently known.
Arrangement
This collection brings together six record groups that are arranged chronologically, one per graduating class. However, since some materials are placed in a class record group based on when they were created, and not by whom, materials relelvant to a class may exist in more than one series.
Scope and Contents
The Classes of 2001-2006 records consist of individual class notes, examinations, papers and class letters, correspondence, photographs, scrapbooks, songbooks as well as reunion materials of the same nature, all related to or dating from the time periods during which these classes were students at Smith College.
Biographical / Historical
College Archives has been collecting class material dating back to the Class of 1879. Classes of 2001-2006 records combine the student material from those graduating classes into one record group.
Smith College--Alumni and alumnae; Smith College--Students.; Smith College. Class of 2002.; Smith College. Class of 2003.; Smith College. Class of 2004.; Smith College. Class of 2005.; Smith College. Class of 2006.; Smith College--Students.; Smith College--Alumni and alumnae
- Class of 2001 Records, 1997-2001; .42 linear feet (1 box)
  - Commencement, 2001 (Box 2313, Folder 1)
  - Commencement- Class President's Speech, 2001 (Box 2313, Folder 2)
  - Last Chapel Awards, 2001 (Box 2313, Folder 3)
  - Who's Who, 1997-1998 (Box 2313, Folder 4)
- Class of 2002 Records, 1998-2004; .42 linear feet (1 archive letter box)
  - Commencement, 2002 (Box 2314, Folder 1)
  - Ivy Day, 2002 (Box 2314, Folder 2)
  - Newsletter, 2004 (Box 2314, Folder 3)
  - Journeys of Discovery, 1998 (Box 2314, Folder 4)
  - Service of Remembrance, 2002 (Box 2314, Folder 5)
- Class of 2003 Records, 1999-2003; .42 linear feet (1 archive letter box)
  - Baccalaureate Service, 2003 (Box 2315, Folder 1)
  - Commencement, 2003 (Box 2315, Folder 2)
  - Commencement Speaker-Madeleine Albright, 2003 (Box 2315, Folder 3)
  - Memory Cards, 2003 (Box 2315, Folder 4)
  - Honorary Degrees, 2003 (Box 2315, Folder 5)
  - Ivy Day, 2003 (Box 2315, Folder 6)
  - Journeys of Discovery, 1999 (Box 2315, Folder 7)
  - New Student Record, 1999 (Box 2315, Folder 8)
  - Reunion Program, 2003 (Box 2315, Folder 9)
- Class of 2004 Records, 2000-2004; .42 linear feet (1 archival letter box)
  - Commencement, 2004 (Box 2316, Folder 1)
  - Convocation, 2004 (Box 2316, Folder 2)
  - Last Chapel, 2004 (Box 2316, Folder 3)
  - Reunion, 2004 (Box 2316, Folder 4)
- Class of 2005 Records, 2001-2005; .92 linear feet (1 archive letter box, 2 archive half-letter boxes)
  - Commencement, 2005 (Box 2317, Folder 1)
  - Commencement Speaker, 2005 (Box 2317, Folder 2)
  - Last Chapel, 2005 (Box 2317, Folder 3)
  - Hyun Joo Chung - Class notes and date planners, 2001-2002 (Box 2317.1)
  - Hyun Joo Chung, 2001-2002 (Box 2317.2)
- Class of 2006 Records, 2002-2006; .5 linear feet (1 archive letter box)
  - Commencement, 2006 (Box 2318)
  - Last Chapel, 2006 (Box 2318)
  - New Student Record, 2002 (Box 2318)